---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=500&category=29&type=multiple
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.0.1
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:02:30 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=5014d252adc978132aff62285b537833; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        is Batman?","correct_answer":"Bruce Wayne","incorrect_answers":["Clark Kent","Barry
        Allen","Tony Stark"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        Marvel Comics, Taurus is the founder and leader of which criminal organization?","correct_answer":"Zodiac","incorrect_answers":["Scorpio","Tiger
        Mafia","The Union"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What&#039;s
        the name of Batman&#039;s parents?","correct_answer":"Thomas &amp; Martha","incorrect_answers":["Joey
        &amp; Jackie","Jason &amp; Sarah","Todd &amp; Mira"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is the creator
        of the comic series &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;?","correct_answer":"Robert
        Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan Lee","Malcolm Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert
        Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        was the name of the first Robin in the Batman comics?","correct_answer":"Dick
        Grayson","incorrect_answers":["Bruce Wayne","Jason Todd","Tim Drake"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the name
        of the comic about a young boy, and a tiger who is actually a stuffed animal?","correct_answer":"Calvin
        and Hobbes","incorrect_answers":["Winnie the Pooh","Albert and Pogo","Peanuts"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In what Homestuck
        Update was [S] Game Over released?","correct_answer":"October 25th, 2014","incorrect_answers":["April
        13th, 2009","April 8th, 2012","August 28th, 2003"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Homestuck
        Series, what is the alternate name for the Kingdom of Lights?","correct_answer":"Prospit","incorrect_answers":["No
        Name","Golden City","Yellow Moon"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"This
        Marvel superhero is often called &quot;The man without fear&quot;.","correct_answer":"Daredevil","incorrect_answers":["Thor","Wolverine","Hulk"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Pre-Super Genesis
        universe of &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic, what was the name of  Sally
        Acorn&#039;s brother?","correct_answer":"Elias Acorn","incorrect_answers":["Maximillian
        Acorn","Alexis Acorn","Frederick Acorn"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which
        issue of the &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic did Scourge the Hedgehog
        make his first appearance?","correct_answer":"Sonic the Hedgehog #11","incorrect_answers":["Sonic
        Universe #32","Sonic the Hedgehog #161","Sonic the Hedgehog #47"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which universe crossover
        was introduced in the &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic issue #247?","correct_answer":"Mega
        Man","incorrect_answers":["Super Mario Brothers","Alex Kidd","Super Monkey
        Ball"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who
        wrote the Batman comic series &quot;The Killing Joke&quot;?","correct_answer":"Alan
        Moore","incorrect_answers":["Bill Finger","Frank Miller","Jerry Siegel"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"When was the Garfield
        comic first published?","correct_answer":"1978","incorrect_answers":["1982","1973","1988"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who authored The
        Adventures of Tintin?","correct_answer":"Herg&eacute;","incorrect_answers":["E.P.
        Jacobs","Rin Tin Tin","Chic Young"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the designation given to the Marvel Cinematic Universe?","correct_answer":"Earth-199999","incorrect_answers":["Earth-616","Earth-10005","Earth-2008"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who created Ultron
        of Earth-616?","correct_answer":"Henry Pym","incorrect_answers":["Amadeus
        Cho","Tony Stark","Reed Richards"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the real hair colour of the mainstream comic book version (Earth-616) of
        Daredevil?","correct_answer":"Blonde","incorrect_answers":["Auburn","Brown","Black"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In what year did
        the first &quot;The Walking Dead&quot; comic come out?","correct_answer":"2003","incorrect_answers":["2001","2006","1999"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the comics,
        which Sonic character took command of the Dark Legion after Luger&#039;s assassination?","correct_answer":"Lien-Da","incorrect_answers":["Kragok","Dimitri","Remington"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the &quot;Archie&quot;
        comics, who was Jughead&#039;s first girlfriend?","correct_answer":"Joani","incorrect_answers":["Ethel","Debbi","Margret"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the alter-ego
        of the DC comics character &quot;Superman&quot;?","correct_answer":"Clark
        Kent","incorrect_answers":["Bruce Wayne","Arthur Curry","John Jones"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which &quot;Green
        Arrow&quot; sidekick commonly wears a baseball cap?","correct_answer":"Roy
        Harper","incorrect_answers":["Black Canary","Emiko Queen","Dick Grayson"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which Batman sidekick
        is the son of Talia al Ghul?","correct_answer":"Damian Wayne","incorrect_answers":["Dick
        Grayson","Tim Drake","Jason Todd"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        the DC Comics 2016 reboot, Rebirth, which speedster escaped from the Speed
        Force after he had been erased from existance?","correct_answer":"Wally West","incorrect_answers":["Johnny
        Quick","Jay Garrick","Eobard Thawne"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the full first name of the babysitter in Calvin and Hobbes?","correct_answer":"Rosalyn","incorrect_answers":["Rose","Ruby","Rachel"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Calvin and
        Hobbes, what is the name of the babysitter&#039;s boyfriend?","correct_answer":"Charlie","incorrect_answers":["Dave","Charles","Nathaniel"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main six year
        old protagonist in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what theologian?","correct_answer":"John
        Calvin","incorrect_answers":["Calvin Klein","Calvin Coolidge","Phillip Calvin
        McGraw"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"The
        stuffed tiger in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what philosopher?","correct_answer":"Thomas
        Hobbes","incorrect_answers":["David Hobbes","John Hobbes","Nathaniel Hobbes"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Calvin and
        Hobbes, what is the name of Susie&#039;s stuffed rabbit?","correct_answer":"Mr.
        Bun","incorrect_answers":["Mr. Bunbun","Mr. Rabbit","Mr. Hoppy"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Calvin and
        Hobbes, what is the name of the principal at Calvin&#039;s school?","correct_answer":"Mr.
        Spittle","incorrect_answers":["Mr. Boreman","Mr. Spitling","Mr. Moe"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"When Batman trolls
        the online chat rooms, what alias does he use?","correct_answer":"JonDoe297","incorrect_answers":["iAmBatman","BWayne13","BW1129"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In 1978, Superman
        teamed up with what celebrity, to defeat an alien invasion?","correct_answer":"Muhammad
        Ali","incorrect_answers":["Mike Tyson","Sylvester Stallone","Arnold Schwarzenegger"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who was the inspiration
        for Cuthbert Calculus in the Tintin series?","correct_answer":"Auguste Picard","incorrect_answers":["Jacques
        Piccard","Will Morris","J. Cecil Maby"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the real name of the &quot;Master Of Magnetism&quot; Magneto?","correct_answer":"Max
        Eisenhardt","incorrect_answers":["Charles Xavier","Pietro Maximoff","Johann
        Schmidt"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        are the names of the two &quot;Canon fan trolls&quot; in &quot;Homestuck&quot;?","correct_answer":"Mierfa
        Durgas and Nektan Whelan","incorrect_answers":["The Wrycrown and Voksea Olkido","Aikter
        Frekik and Xagrai Ollomu","Grekei Ceknux and Riya Camacho"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Homestuck&quot;
        what is Dave Strider&#039;s guardian?","correct_answer":"Bro","incorrect_answers":["Becquerel","Doc
        Scratch","Halley"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        Bionicle, who was formerly a Av-Matoran and is now the Toa of Light?","correct_answer":"Takua","incorrect_answers":["Jaller","Vakama","Tahu"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Found in the Marvel
        Comics fictional universe, what is the name of the nearly indestructible metal
        that coats Wolverine&#039;s bones and claws?","correct_answer":"Adamantium","incorrect_answers":["Titanium","Vibranium","Carbonadium"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"When was Marvel
        Comics founded?","correct_answer":"1939","incorrect_answers":["1932","1951","1936"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is Homestuck
        character Gamzee&#039;s last name?","correct_answer":"Makara","incorrect_answers":["Makera","Makare","Makrea"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Better known by
        his nickname Logan, what is Wolverine&#039;s birth name?","correct_answer":"James
        Howlett","incorrect_answers":["Logan Wolf","Thomas Wilde","John Savage"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What are the Three
        Virtues of Bionicle?","correct_answer":"Unity, Duty, Destiny","incorrect_answers":["Build,
        Play, Change","Work, Play, Live","Forge, Build, Fight"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is Hellboy&#039;s
        true name?","correct_answer":"Anung Un Rama","incorrect_answers":["Right Hand
        of Doom","Ogdru Jahad","Azzael"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In
        the Hellboy universe, what was Abe Sapien&#039;s birth name?","correct_answer":"Langdon
        Everett Caul","incorrect_answers":["Lord Baltimore","Sir Edward Grey","Landis
        Pope"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        Black Hammer, what dimension does Colonel Weird travel through?","correct_answer":"Para-Zone","incorrect_answers":["Hyperspace","Mirror
        Universe","Phantom Zone"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What&#039;s
        the race of Invincible&#039;s father?","correct_answer":"Viltrumite","incorrect_answers":["Kryptonian","Kree","Irken"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which one of these
        superhero teams appears in the Invincible comics?","correct_answer":"Guardians
        of the Globe","incorrect_answers":["Avengers","Justice League","Teenage Mutant
        Ninja Turtles"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who
        was the first American Vampire (Scott Snyder&#039;s American Vampire)?","correct_answer":"Skinner
        Sweet","incorrect_answers":["Hattie Hargrove","Pearl Jones","James &quot;Jim&quot;
        Book"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What&#039;s
        the weakness of american vampires (Scott Snyder&#039;s American Vampire)?","correct_answer":"Gold","incorrect_answers":["Sunlight","Wood","Silver"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:02:30 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=500&category=29&type=multiple
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.0.1
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:02:30 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=8d745a06649b4b6e549d13fb61e072c1; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        is Batman?","correct_answer":"Bruce Wayne","incorrect_answers":["Clark Kent","Barry
        Allen","Tony Stark"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        Marvel Comics, Taurus is the founder and leader of which criminal organization?","correct_answer":"Zodiac","incorrect_answers":["Scorpio","Tiger
        Mafia","The Union"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What&#039;s
        the name of Batman&#039;s parents?","correct_answer":"Thomas &amp; Martha","incorrect_answers":["Joey
        &amp; Jackie","Jason &amp; Sarah","Todd &amp; Mira"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Batman comics,
        by what other name is the villain Dr. Jonathan Crane known?","correct_answer":"Scarecrow","incorrect_answers":["Bane","Calendar
        Man","Clayface"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        is the creator of the comic series &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;?","correct_answer":"Robert
        Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan Lee","Malcolm Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert
        Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        was the name of the first Robin in the Batman comics?","correct_answer":"Dick
        Grayson","incorrect_answers":["Bruce Wayne","Jason Todd","Tim Drake"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the name
        of the main character in the webcomic Gunnerkrigg Court by Tom Siddell?","correct_answer":"Antimony","incorrect_answers":["Bismuth","Mercury","Cobalt"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In what Homestuck
        Update was [S] Game Over released?","correct_answer":"October 25th, 2014","incorrect_answers":["April
        13th, 2009","April 8th, 2012","August 28th, 2003"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Homestuck
        Series, what is the alternate name for the Kingdom of Lights?","correct_answer":"Prospit","incorrect_answers":["No
        Name","Golden City","Yellow Moon"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which
        of the following superheros did Wonder Woman NOT have a love interest in?","correct_answer":"Green
        Arrow","incorrect_answers":["Superman","Batman","Steve Trevor"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"This Marvel superhero
        is often called &quot;The man without fear&quot;.","correct_answer":"Daredevil","incorrect_answers":["Thor","Wolverine","Hulk"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Pre-Super Genesis
        universe of &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic, what was the name of  Sally
        Acorn&#039;s brother?","correct_answer":"Elias Acorn","incorrect_answers":["Maximillian
        Acorn","Alexis Acorn","Frederick Acorn"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic, who was the creator of Roboticizer?
        ","correct_answer":"Professor Charles the Hedgehog","incorrect_answers":["Julian
        Robotnik","Ivo Robotnik","Snively Robotnik"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which universe crossover
        was introduced in the &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic issue #247?","correct_answer":"Mega
        Man","incorrect_answers":["Super Mario Brothers","Alex Kidd","Super Monkey
        Ball"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who
        wrote the Batman comic series &quot;The Killing Joke&quot;?","correct_answer":"Alan
        Moore","incorrect_answers":["Bill Finger","Frank Miller","Jerry Siegel"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the designation
        given to the Marvel Cinematic Universe?","correct_answer":"Earth-199999","incorrect_answers":["Earth-616","Earth-10005","Earth-2008"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who created Ultron
        of Earth-616?","correct_answer":"Henry Pym","incorrect_answers":["Amadeus
        Cho","Tony Stark","Reed Richards"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the real hair colour of the mainstream comic book version (Earth-616) of
        Daredevil?","correct_answer":"Blonde","incorrect_answers":["Auburn","Brown","Black"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In what year did
        the first &quot;The Walking Dead&quot; comic come out?","correct_answer":"2003","incorrect_answers":["2001","2006","1999"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the comics,
        which Sonic character took command of the Dark Legion after Luger&#039;s assassination?","correct_answer":"Lien-Da","incorrect_answers":["Kragok","Dimitri","Remington"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the &quot;Archie&quot;
        comics, who was Jughead&#039;s first girlfriend?","correct_answer":"Joani","incorrect_answers":["Ethel","Debbi","Margret"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the alter-ego
        of the DC comics character &quot;Superman&quot;?","correct_answer":"Clark
        Kent","incorrect_answers":["Bruce Wayne","Arthur Curry","John Jones"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which Batman sidekick
        is the son of Talia al Ghul?","correct_answer":"Damian Wayne","incorrect_answers":["Dick
        Grayson","Tim Drake","Jason Todd"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        the DC Comics 2016 reboot, Rebirth, which speedster escaped from the Speed
        Force after he had been erased from existance?","correct_answer":"Wally West","incorrect_answers":["Johnny
        Quick","Jay Garrick","Eobard Thawne"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the full first name of the babysitter in Calvin and Hobbes?","correct_answer":"Rosalyn","incorrect_answers":["Rose","Ruby","Rachel"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Calvin and
        Hobbes, what is the name of the babysitter&#039;s boyfriend?","correct_answer":"Charlie","incorrect_answers":["Dave","Charles","Nathaniel"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main six year
        old protagonist in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what theologian?","correct_answer":"John
        Calvin","incorrect_answers":["Calvin Klein","Calvin Coolidge","Phillip Calvin
        McGraw"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"The
        stuffed tiger in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what philosopher?","correct_answer":"Thomas
        Hobbes","incorrect_answers":["David Hobbes","John Hobbes","Nathaniel Hobbes"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Calvin and
        Hobbes, what is the name of Susie&#039;s stuffed rabbit?","correct_answer":"Mr.
        Bun","incorrect_answers":["Mr. Bunbun","Mr. Rabbit","Mr. Hoppy"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Calvin and
        Hobbes, what is the name of the principal at Calvin&#039;s school?","correct_answer":"Mr.
        Spittle","incorrect_answers":["Mr. Boreman","Mr. Spitling","Mr. Moe"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"When Batman trolls
        the online chat rooms, what alias does he use?","correct_answer":"JonDoe297","incorrect_answers":["iAmBatman","BWayne13","BW1129"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In 1978, Superman
        teamed up with what celebrity, to defeat an alien invasion?","correct_answer":"Muhammad
        Ali","incorrect_answers":["Mike Tyson","Sylvester Stallone","Arnold Schwarzenegger"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who was the inspiration
        for Cuthbert Calculus in the Tintin series?","correct_answer":"Auguste Picard","incorrect_answers":["Jacques
        Piccard","Will Morris","J. Cecil Maby"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which
        of the following rings from the DC Comics&#039; &quot;Lantern Corps&quot;
        are classified as Parasitic?","correct_answer":"Indigo (Compassion)","incorrect_answers":["Green
        (Willpower)","White (Life)","Yellow (Fear)"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the real
        name of the &quot;Master Of Magnetism&quot; Magneto?","correct_answer":"Max
        Eisenhardt","incorrect_answers":["Charles Xavier","Pietro Maximoff","Johann
        Schmidt"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        &quot;Homestuck&quot; what is Dave Strider&#039;s guardian?","correct_answer":"Bro","incorrect_answers":["Becquerel","Doc
        Scratch","Halley"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Found
        in the Marvel Comics fictional universe, what is the name of the nearly indestructible
        metal that coats Wolverine&#039;s bones and claws?","correct_answer":"Adamantium","incorrect_answers":["Titanium","Vibranium","Carbonadium"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"When was Marvel
        Comics founded?","correct_answer":"1939","incorrect_answers":["1932","1951","1936"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is Homestuck
        character Gamzee&#039;s last name?","correct_answer":"Makara","incorrect_answers":["Makera","Makare","Makrea"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Better known by
        his nickname Logan, what is Wolverine&#039;s birth name?","correct_answer":"James
        Howlett","incorrect_answers":["Logan Wolf","Thomas Wilde","John Savage"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What are the Three
        Virtues of Bionicle?","correct_answer":"Unity, Duty, Destiny","incorrect_answers":["Build,
        Play, Change","Work, Play, Live","Forge, Build, Fight"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the Hellboy
        universe, who founded the BPRD?","correct_answer":"Trevor Bruttenholm","incorrect_answers":["Kate
        Corrigan","Johann Kraus","Benjamin Daimio"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is Hellboy&#039;s true name?","correct_answer":"Anung Un Rama","incorrect_answers":["Right
        Hand of Doom","Ogdru Jahad","Azzael"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In
        the Hellboy universe, what was Abe Sapien&#039;s birth name?","correct_answer":"Langdon
        Everett Caul","incorrect_answers":["Lord Baltimore","Sir Edward Grey","Landis
        Pope"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        Black Hammer, what city did the heroes save from the Anti-God?","correct_answer":"Spiral
        City","incorrect_answers":["Mega-City One","Rockwood","Star City"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Black Hammer,
        what dimension does Colonel Weird travel through?","correct_answer":"Para-Zone","incorrect_answers":["Hyperspace","Mirror
        Universe","Phantom Zone"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What&#039;s
        the race of Invincible&#039;s father?","correct_answer":"Viltrumite","incorrect_answers":["Kryptonian","Kree","Irken"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which one of these
        superhero teams appears in the Invincible comics?","correct_answer":"Guardians
        of the Globe","incorrect_answers":["Avengers","Justice League","Teenage Mutant
        Ninja Turtles"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who
        was the first American Vampire (Scott Snyder&#039;s American Vampire)?","correct_answer":"Skinner
        Sweet","incorrect_answers":["Hattie Hargrove","Pearl Jones","James &quot;Jim&quot;
        Book"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What&#039;s
        the weakness of american vampires (Scott Snyder&#039;s American Vampire)?","correct_answer":"Gold","incorrect_answers":["Sunlight","Wood","Silver"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:02:30 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.0.0
